Guide to the Nancy Hanks Papers, 1894-1987 (bulk 1945-1983)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal Series, 1927-1983and undated(bulk 1940s-1970s)(59 boxes).
  - Correspondence
    - Sarratt, Martha, 1960-1967, undated (Box 127)
    - Shaw, Dorothy Patricia, 1949-1950, undated (Box 127)
    - Sites, Crawford, 1948-1950 (Box 127)
    - Smith, Bobbe, 1979-1982 (Box 127)
    - Smith, Preston, 1950, 1972-1975 (Box 127)
    - Stewart, Verna, 1957-1960, 1971-1977 (Box 127)
    - T, 1949-1982, undated (Box 128)
    - Thomas, Jett, 1948-1950 (Box 128)
    - Thrailkill, Jane, 1945-1972, undated (Box 128)
    - U, 1973-1981 (Box 128)
    - V, 1960-1981, undated (Box 128)
    - W, 1949-1982, undated, (3 folders) (Box 128)
    - Walker, Dave, 1948-1956, undated (Box 128)
    - Walton, Betty Bob and Loring, 1949-1959, undated (Box 129)
    - Watkins, John, 1949-1959 (Box 129)
    - Williams, Ron, 1981-1983, undated (Box 129)
    - Wilson, John, 1949-1951 (Box 129)
    - X-Z, 1959-1982, undated (Box 129)
    - Miscellaneous:
      - Hanks, Bryan C: Death, 1972 (Box 129)
      - Hanks, Nancy: Illness, 1974 (Box 129)
      - Sympathy notes, 1972-1973 (Box 129)
      - First name only, undated (Box 129)
      - Unidentified, 1948-1981 and undated (Box 129)
  - Financial Papers
    - Bank records, 1974-1978, (7 folders) (Box 130)
    - Expenses (reimbursed and unreimbursed), 1975-1978, (4 folders) (Box 131)
    - Medical, 1952-1978, (5 folders) (Box 131)
    - Real Estate:
      - Carillon House, 1951 (Box 131)
      - 24 West 55th St., 1955-1960 (Box 131)
      - Southampton, Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970, 1976, undated (Box 131)
      - Southampton, 1976 May 26-28 (Box 132)
      - 930 Fifth Ave., 1960-1979, (3 folders) (Box 132)
      - 1236 30th St., 1969-1979, (2 folders) (Box 132)
      - Watergate, 1974-1981, undated (Box 132)
      - 3265 N St., N.W., 1978-1980 (Box 132)
    - Stocks, A-R, (3 folders) (Box 132)
    - Stocks:
      - S-Z (Box 132)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1981, undated (Box 132)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1982, undated, (2 folders) (Box 132)
    - Tax papers, 1951-1963, (10 folders) (Box 132)
    - Tax papers, 1964-1981 1964-1981, (9 folders) (Box 134)
    - Miscellaneous (City Tavern Club), 1973-1982 (Box 134)
    - Miscellaneous: (Box 135)
      - (Cosmopolitan Club), 1979-1981 (Box 135)
      - General, 1957-1981, undated (Box 135)
      - Property taxes, 1974-1982 (Box 135)
  - Scrapbooks, 1949, 1951
    - Speeches
      - 1977-1979 May (Box 135)
      - 1979 Dec.-1982, (4 folders) (Box 136)
      - Background material, 1971-1981 (Box 136)
    - Student Papers
      - Junior-Senior High School, 1934-1945 (Box 136)
      - High School Yearbook, 1945 (Box 137)
      - Duke Univeristy, Papers, 1945-1949 (Box 137)
      - Duke University:
        - Address books, 1948-1949, undated (Box 137)
        - Calendars, 1947-1949 (Box 137)
        - Notebooks, 1946, undated (Box 137)
      - Duke University, Scrapbook, 1946-1947 (Box 138)
      - Oxford University, 1948 (Box 138)
  - Miscellaneous, 1944-1982, undated, (2 folders)
    - Alphabetical
      - Aspen Institute, 1977-1979 (Box 139)
      - Cleaners, 1977-1981 (Box 139)
      - Council and Conference for the Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 139)
      - Keepsake Items of Nancy Hanks, 1939-1981 and undated (Box 139)
      - Luce (Henry) Foundation, 1982 (Box 139)
      - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1981 (Box 139)
    - Correspondence
      - Furst, Dr. William, 1953 Apr.-Dec. (Box 139)
      - Hanks-Kester Trip, 1957-1965, (2 folders) (Box 139)
      - Landau, Sonia, 1977-1979 (Box 139)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1959-1967 (Box 139)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1954-1977, undated (Box 140)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1977 (Box 140)
    - Financial Papers
      - Stocks: Nancy Hanks, 1954-1961 (Box 140)
- Friends of the Nancy Hanks Center, Inc. Series, 1971-1987(13 boxes).
  Cassette tapes, videocassettes, correspondence, questionnaires, and interviews. Major categories: interviews (transcripts and cassette tapes), questionnaires, and Old Post Office building. Interviews and questionnaires arranged alphabetically by surname. Categories arranged alphabetically. Some interviews are restricted.
  Many of the interviews in this series also exist as electronic files dispersed throughout twenty-one computer disks. Disks were assigned consecutive numbers reflecting the original order in which they were received. If an interview has an identical electronic file(s), the file is included in the alphabetical list below. In such cases, the electronic file's name is listed, followed by the year of the interview, then the file's disk (subdirectory) name.
  The contents of each disk was migrated to the Specoll server. Consequently, the text of these electronic files is available in correspondingly numbered electronic subdirectories. Consult a reference archivist for access to the electronic files.
  - Audio Visual: An American Portrait, 1985, Dec. 19 (Box 141)
  - Interviews: Tapes, A-GA (Box 142)
  - Interviews: Tapes, Gi-Mitchell (Box 143)
  - Interviews: Tapes, Mitchell-Thrailkill (Box 144)
  - Interviews: Tapes, Alexion-Steele (RESTRICTED) (Box 145)
  - Interviews and Transcripts (Box 146)
    - Aaron, Chloe (Box 146)
    - Allen, Raye Virginia, (2 folders)
      - Allen.b, Allen.c, Allen.d and Allen.e, 1986 (on Disk007), Allen.2a, Allen.2b, Allen.2c and Allen.2d, 1986(on Disk002), Allen.e and Allen.f, 1986 (on Disk006) (Box 146)
    - Anderson, Walter (Box 146)
    - Arey, June
      - Arey.a, Arey.b and Arey.c, 1986, on Disk008 (Box 146)
    - Baber, Adin
      - Baber.a, 1984, on Disk013 (Box 146)
    - Benedict, Stephen
      - Benedict.1a, Benedict.1b and Benedict.1c, 1985, on Disk016 (Box 146)
    - Biddle, Livingston
      - Biddle.2a, 1985, on Disk012 (Box 146)
    - Bishopric, Anne
      - Bishop.a and Bishop.b, 1986, on Disk014 (Box 146)
    - Burnett, Nancy Hanks
      - Burnett.a, undated, on Disk003 (Box 146)
    - Clark, Tobe (Box 146)
    - Creel, Dana (in electronic format only)
      - Creel.a and Creel.b, 1986, on Disk015 (Box 146)
    - Duke, Leilani Lattin
      - Duke.a, Duke.b and Duke.c, 1987, on Disk011 (Box 146)
    - Eells, William
      - Eels.a and Eels.b, 1986, on Disk020 (Box 146)
    - Fisher, Pat (Box 146)
    - Furst, William
      - Furst.a, 1985, on Disk013 (Box 146)
  - Interviews and Transcripts (Box 147)
    - Garment, Leonard
      - Garment.1a, 1985 (on Disk012) and Garment.2a, 1986 (on Disk013) (Box 147)
    - Gillespie, Dorothy
      - Gillespi.a, 1984, on Disk003 (Box 147)
    - Golodner, Jack
      - Gol.a and Gol.b, 1985, on Disk001 (Box 147)
    - Gracey, Janet
      - Gracey.a and Gracey.b, 1985, on Disk014 (Box 147)
    - Hansen, Orval
      - Hansen.a, 1986, on Disk001 (Box 147)
    - Hayes, Helen
      - Hayes.a, 1986, on Disk009 (Box 147)
    - Horowitz, Harold (Box 147)
    - Irwin, George
      - Irwin.a, Irwin.b, Irwin.c and Irwin.d, 1986, on Disk019 (Box 147)
    - Kane, Constance
      - Kane.a, undated, on Disk003 (Box 147)
    - Kennedy, John R.
      - Kennedy.1a, 1984, on Disk012 (Box 147)
    - Kissinger, Henry
      - Kissinge.a, 1986, on Disk009 (Box 147)
    - Krakora, Polly (Box 147)
    - Kyros, Peter
      - Kyros.2a and Kyros.2b, 1985, on Disk015 (Box 147)
    - Lacy, Bill
      - Lacy.1a and Lacy.1b, 1985, on Disk015 (Box 147)
    - Lazarus, Mr. and Mrs. Fred, III and James Edgy
      - Lazarus.a, Lazarus.b, Lazarus.c and Lazarus.d, 1986, on Disk021 (Box 147)
    - Lazarus, Fred, III
      - Lazarus.1a, Lazarus.1b and Lazarus.1c, 1985, on Disk019 (Box 147)
    - Lazarus, Fred, IV (Box 147)
    - Lowry, McNeil
      - Lowry.a and Lowry.b, 1985, on Disk005 (Box 147)
    - Mark, Charles (Box 147)
    - Mayleas, Ruth
      - Bak.aa, 1985, on Disk013 (Box 147)
  - Interviews and Transcripts (Box 148)
    - Mitchell, Donna, (5 folders)
      - Mitchell.4a and Mitchell.4b, 1986 (on Disk008), Mitchell.a, Mitchell.b and Mitchell.c, 1986 (on Disk009), Thrail.3a, Thrail.3b and Thrail.3c, 1986 (on Disk017) (Box 148)
    - Mitchell, Mr. and Mrs.
      - Mitchell.a, 1986, on Disk001 (Box 148)
    - Mitze, Clark
      - Mitze.a, 1986, on Disk015 (Box 148)
    - Murphy, Anne (Box 148)
    - Pell, Claiborne
      - Pell.1a, 1985, on Disk012 (Box 148)
    - Randolph, Leonard
      - Randolph.2a, Randolph.2b and Randolph.2c, 1986, on Disk020, (3 folders) (Box 148)
    - Reger, Lawrence
      - Reger.a, Reger.b and Reger.c, 1985, on Disk001 (Box 148)
    - Rice, Leroy and Nell (Box 148)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance
      - Rock.1a and Rock.1b, 1986, on Disk015 (Box 148)
    - Ruebhausen, Oscar
      - Rueb.a, 1986, on Disk009 (Box 148)
    - Rutledge, Jay (Box 148)
  - Interviews and Transcripts (Box 149)
    - Sell, Steve
      - Sell.1a and Sell.1b, 1986, on Disk017 (Box 149)
    - Semans, Mary
      - Semans.a and Semans.b, 1986, on Disk006 (Box 149)
    - Sheets, Robert
      - Sheets.a and Sheets.b, 1986, on Disk014 (Box 149)
    - Spencer, John
      - Spencer.a and Spencer.b, 1986, on Disk006 (Box 149)
    - Thomas, John
      - Thomas.a, 1985, on Disk013 (Box 149)
    - Thompson, Frank (Box 149)
    - Thrailkill, Jane, (2 folders)
      - Thrail.2a, 1984 (on Disk010), Thrail.1a and Thrail.1b, 1985 (on Disk016), Thrail.3a, Thrail.3b and Thrail.3c, 1986 (on Disk017), Thrail.3d and Thrail.3e, 1986(on Disk008) (Box 149)
    - Weil, Elizabeth
      - Weil.a and Weil.b, 1986, on Disk020 (Box 149)
    - Weil, Suzanne
      - Weil.a and Weil.b, 1985, on Disk009 (Box 149)
    - Whitfield, Vantile
      - Whit.2a, 1985 (on Disk001) and Whit.2b, 1985 (on Disk002) (Box 149)
    - Williams, Nadia
      - Williams.a, Williams.b and Williams.c, 1986, on Disk004 (Box 149)
  - Interviews and Transcripts; Questionnnaires (RESTRICTED) (Box 150)
    - Brademas, John
      - Brademas.a and Brademas.b, 1986, on Disk018 (Box 150)
    - Lowe, Florence (Box 150)
    - Prince, Joseph and Marjorielaine
      - Prince.1a and Prince.1b, 1985 (on Disk010) and Prince.1c, 1985 (on Disk018) (Box 150)
    - Steele, Ana (Clark) (Box 150)
  - Questionnaires (RESTRICTED)
    - Reilly, William K. (Box 150)
    - Lee, Maryat (Box 150)
  - Old Post Office (Box 151)
    - Bills, Public Laws, Congressional Records, 1972-1976, undated (Box 151)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1986, (3 folders) (Box 151)
    - Dedication, 1986, Oct. (Box 151)
    - Memorial Proposals, undated (Box 151)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972-1986, undated, (2 folders) (Box 151)
    - Statements, 1971-1977, undated
      - Photographs, 1971-1977 (Box 151)
  - Questionnaires (Box 152)
    - A-G, (3 folders) (Box 152)
    - Ford, Gerald R. (Box 152)
    - Gaus, David S. (Box 152)
    - Graham, Florence (Box 152)
    - Gray, Barbara Ann (Box 152)
    - Guyton, John (Box 152)
    - H-L, (3 folders) (Box 152)
  - Questionnaires (Box 153)
    - M (Box 153)
    - Mavis, Sylvia (Box 153)
    - Mitchell, Donna and Victor (Box 153)
    - Morris, Mabel and Frank (Box 153)
    - N-R (Box 153)
    - Pell, Claiborne (Box 153)
    - Riggs, Polly (Box 153)
    - S (Box 153)
    - Sennema, David (Box 153)
    - Stoddard, Richard (Box 153)
    - T-V (Box 153)
    - Ticknor, Jane (Box 153)
    - W-Z (Box 153)
    - Waldrop, Gayle (Box 153)
    - White, Lawrence (Box 153)
    - Wilde, F. B. (Box 153)
- Virginia and Bryan Hanks Series, 1894-1983(bulk 1920s-1983)(8 boxes).
  Chiefly correspondence among Bryan and Virginia, other family members (including Wooding family letters), their friends, and associates. Includes also clippings, legal and financial papers, Virginia Hanks' diaries, patent papers of Benjamin F. Wooding (Virginia's father), family information, and photographs. Categories arranged alphabetically; correspondence arranged chronologically.
  - Clippings, 1972 Dec. (Box 154)
  - Correspondence:
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1894-1931, (7 folders) (Box 154)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1931 (no month)-1932 Mar., (6 folders) (Box 155)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1932 (no month)-1954 Nov., (6 folders) (Box 156)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1955 Feb.-1960 June, (6 folders) (Box 157)
    - Hanks, Virginia and Bryan, 1960 July-1982, (6 folders) (Box 158)
    - Lynn, Herman and Jessie, 1950-1960 (Box 159)
    - Wooding, Benjamin F., 1903-1926 (Box 159)
  - Diaries (Wooding, Virginia), 1918-1922 (Box 159)
  - Family History, 1924-1952 (Box 159)
  - Financial papers, (Virginia's), 1916-1983 (Box 159)
  - Groves, Wallace family, 1953-1967 (Box 159)
  - Legal and financial papers (Wooding, Benjamin F.), 1903-1930 (Box 159)
  - Miami Bribery Case, 1938-1939 (Box 160)
  - Patents of Benjamin F. Wooding, 1924-1929 (Box 160)
  - Photographs: Wooding family and friends, including albumen prints, undated, (2 folders) (Box 160)
  - Photographs: 1936-1977 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 160)
  - Photographs: 1978-1982 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 161)
  - "Virginia Woodings Book--University of Colorado," 1918-1920 (Box 161)
  - Miscellaneous, 1918-1972 and undated (Box 161)
- Larry Hanks Series, 1938-1961(1 box).
  Includes Larry's letters home as well as correspondence about his death, clippings, legal papers, photographs, and brief information about memorial contributions and the Larry Hanks Memorial Foundation. Categories arranged alphabetically.
  - Correspondence, 1938-1958 (Box 162)
  - Claim accounts for Larry Hank's Death, 1950-1952, (2 folders) (Box 162)
  - Larry Hanks Memorial Foundation, 1951-1960, undated (Box 162)
  - Memorial contributions, 1950-1952 (Box 162)
  - Memorial services, 1950 (Box 162)
  - Photographs, 1932-1950, undated (Box 162)
  - Southwestern University, 1949-1961, undated (Box 162)
  - Miscellaneous, 1931-1951, undated (Box 162)
- Pictures Series, 1927-1982and undated(6 boxes).
  Photographs (some oversize), slides, and photograph albums. Includes pictures of Nancy Hanks, her parents and brother, her college years, homes, trips, and National Endowment for the Arts, pre-NEA work with Nelson Rockefeller, and with President Gerald R. Ford. Arranged alphabetically by person or topic.
  - Hanks, Nancy, 1927-1982, (3 folders) (Box 163)
  - Family, undated (Box 163)
  - College, 1945-1948 (Box 163)
  - College Photograph Album, 1946-1948, (2 folders) (Box 164)
  - Homes (Photo Albums):
    - The Mountain House, 1939 (Box 164)
    - North Carolina, Cashiers, 1952-1981 (Box 164)
    - Miami, 1936, 1978; Key Largo, 1938, 1960, 1973 (Box 164)
    - Southhampton, CT: Danbury; New Jersey: Montclair; Washington, DC (Box 164)
  - Trips:
    - 1959-1972, undated (Box 164)
    - California scrapbook, 1950 (Box 164)
  - Pre-NEA, work with Rockefeller, Nelson, 1955-1960s (Box 164)
  - Album/scrapbook, 1960s (Box 164)
  - NEA: (Box 165)
    - 1970-1974, undated, (5 folders) (Box 165)
    - Annenberg Center Dedication, University of Pennsylvania, 1971 Apr. 8 (Box 165)
    - RIAA Cultural Award Dinner, 1971 Mar. 25 (Box 165)
    - Screening of "See/Touch/Feel," 1971 Jan. 26 (Box 165)
    - Wilderness Exhibition, 1971 Nov. 8 (Box 165)
    - Convention of the American Council of Polish Cultural Clubs, 1972 June 15-17 (Box 165)
    - USC Honorary Degree, 1973 Feb. (Box 165)
    - Symphony Orchestra League Conference, 1974 June (Box 165)
    - Hanks, Nancy and Gerald R. Ford, 1974 Sept. (Box 166)
    - American Federation of Musicians, 1975 June (Box 166)
    - "Overview of NEA, 1965-1977" (Box 166)
    - Photograph Album, 1965-1968, (3 folders) (Box 166)
    - Scrapbook, 1977 (Box 166)
    - Photographs, miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - Woodrow Wilson, undated (Box 166)
  - Slides: (Box 167)
    - Family, 1952-1962, undated (Box 167)
    - Homes:
      - Cashiers, 1950-1980, undated (Box 167)
      - Hank homes and art, 1951-1968 (Box 167)
    - Trips, 1950-1967, undated (Box 167)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1977 (Box 167)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1954-1955 (Box 168)
  - Slides, Miscellaneous, 1954, undated (Box 168)
- Awards and Memorabilia Series, 1955-1982and undated(5 boxes).
  Categories: awards and honorary degrees, and official inscribed personal items. Includes a list of honorary degrees that Hanks declined. Contains certificates; silver boxes, cups, and tray; ashtrays, mounted photographs, bronze medallions and sculptures, keys to various cities; gold pin and box, plaques, and paperweights. Majority of items in off-site storage.
  - Awards and honorary degrees, 1970-1982 and undated (Box 169)
  - Honorary Degrees Declined, 1973-1977 (Box 169)
  - Personal items, official (Box 170)
    - Silver box, Tiffany ("1955 - N.H. - N.A.R." with U.S. seal), 1955. (Box 170)
    - Picture of Nancy Hanks Lincoln (inscribed "To my cousin Nancy Hanks. Compliments of Adin Baber, undated") (Box 170)
    - Silver julep cups:
      - Inscribed "Nancy Hanks, Lexington, Kentucky", Mar. 17, 1973. (Box 170)
      - inscribed "H.H.D. Centre M. and F. Moosnick", Nov. 2, 1973. (Box 170)
    - Silver box ( Nelson A. Rockefeller), undated (Box 170)
    - Ink pen ( Richard M. Nixon), undated (Box 170)
    - Glass ashtray ( Gerald R. Ford), undated (Box 170)
    - Glass ashtray (Rep. Claude Pepper), undated (Box 170)
    - Shadowbox (mementoes of N.E.A. career), undated (Box 170)
    - Shakespeare festival (silver jubilee award, Old Globe Theatre, San Diego), 1974. (Box 170)
  - Personal items, official (Box 171)
    - Mounted photograph (Inaugural Parade, Jimmy and Rosalyn Carter), undated (Box 171)
    - Mounted photograph ( Pablo Casals and Rudolf Serkin), 1972 (Box 171)
    - Mounted photograph ( John Hoare Kerr), 1978 (Box 171)
  - Awards (Box 172)
    - Bronze medallion ( Municipal Art Society, N.Y.), 1977. (Box 172)
    - "Sower" bronze statue ( Duke University Founders' Society), undated (Box 172)
    - Thomas Jefferson bust ( American Society of Interior Designers Thomas Jefferson Award),1977. (Box 172)
    - Key to the city ( San Francisco), 1975. (Box 172)
    - Key to the city ( Winston-Salem, N.C.), 1970. (Box 172)
    - Key to the city ( Savannah, Ga.), undated (Box 172)
    - Key to the city ( Indianapolis, Ind.), undated (Box 172)
    - Key to the city ( Montgomery, Ala.), undated (Box 172)
    - Key to the city ( Lexington, Ky.), undated (Box 172)
    - Key to the city ( Omaha, Neb.), undated (Box 172)
    - Key to the city ( Fort Worth, Tex.), undated (Box 172)
    - Mayor-president's key ( Baton Rouge, La.), undated (Box 172)
    - Key to Duke University ( Bryan Center Dedication), 1982. (Box 172)
    - Bronze medallion ( Marian Anderson: "Honored by Congress for Public Service through Music"), 1977. (Box 172)
    - Bronze sculpture ( Jose Limon Dance Company - Cultural Productions - U.S.A.), undated (Box 172)
    - Bronze medallion ( Michigan State University), undated (Box 172)
    - Gold pin (Presidential seal), 1970. (Box 172)
    - Bronze medal ( Texas Christian University Centennial), 1973. (Box 172)
    - Gold box ( Youth Orchestra of Fort Worth), 1974. (Box 172)
    - Bronze medallion (Churchill Medal), undated (Box 172)
    - Silver medallion ( Parliament House, New Delhi), undated (Box 172)
    - Signed program ( Founders Award, Partners for Livable Places), 1982. (Box 172)
    - Statue ( Swan Award), 1977. (Box 172)
    - Gold pendant ( Washington University Saint Louis: Inscribed "Nancy Hanks - D.F.A. 5/26/73"), 1973. (Box 172)
    - Silver medallion in Lucite ( The Federalist Society), undated (Box 172)
  - Awards (Box 173)
    - Key to the city ( Providence, R.I.), undated (Box 173)
    - Bronze medallion ( U.S.A. Bicentennial, Finnish Committee), 1976. (Box 173)
    - Brass paperweight ( Minnesota State Arts Council Award), 1973. (Box 173)
    - Silver tray ( Opera America Award), undated (Box 173)
    - Plaque ( Utah State Institute of Fine Arts Award), 1972. (Box 173)
    - Lucite Michigan statue ( Detroit Institute of the Arts), 1975. (Box 173)
    - Plaque ( Association of American Dance Companies), 1978. (Box 173)
    - Plaque ( Arts Management Award), 1978. (Box 173)
    - Trophy base (Order of the Triton IV, University of California, San Diego), 1975. (Box 173)
    - Framed certificate ( National Council of Art Administrators), 1981. (Box 173)
    - Plaque ( Arts and Business Cooperative Council, N.Y. Board of Trade), 1971. (Box 173)
    - Plaque (Visual Communications Today, Univ. of Maryland), undated (Box 173)
    - Metal type in box ( Award of Design Recognition, Federal Design Council), 1975. (Box 173)
    - Bronze medallion ( Louisiana Council of Music and the Performing Arts), 1977. (Box 173)
    - Silver box ("To Nancy Hanks...From All of Her Friends at Lincoln Center"), 1978. (Box 173)
    - Bronze medallion ( City of New York), 1977. (Box 173)
    - Silver box ( Arts Council of Greater Fort Worth), 1970. (Box 173)
- Oversize Materials
  - Miscellaneous oversize folders (1 and 2) (Box 179)
  - Friends of the Nancy Hanks Center, Inc.: Old Post Office: Memorial Proposals (Opaperfolder 4)
  - Personal series: Financial papers: Real estate floor plans (Opaperfolder 5)
  - American Film Institute Series
    - Budget, 1973 (Box 179)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Series
    - Photograph Album: Trips, 1971 (Box 175)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Series
    - Rockefeller, John D., 1978 (Box 174)
  - Personal Series
    - Financial Papers (floor plans), undated (Box 5)
    - Student Papers: High School Photograph Album, 1941-1943 (Box 175)
    - Student Papers: High School Scrapbook, 1941 (Box 176)
      - Student Papers: High School Scrapook, 1942-1943 (Box 176)
  - Friends of the Nancy Hanks Center, Inc. Series
    - Old Post Office Memorial Proposals, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Virginia and Bryan Hanks Series
    - Miami Bribery Case, 1938-1942 (Box 2)
    - Family History, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
    - Virginia and Bryan College Degrees, 1922 (Box 2)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1941-1942 (Box 174)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 174)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 174)
  - Larry Hanks Series
    - Photographs, undated (Box 174)
  - Pictures Series
    - Hanks, Nancy, undated (Box 174)
    - Rockefeller/ NEA, 1955and 1977 (Box 174)
  - Awards and Memorabilia Series
    - Awards and Honorary Degrees, 1959-1981 (Box 1)
    - Framed musical score (20th Anniversary, American Council for the Arts), signed by Bill Schuman, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Enlargement of Washington Post editorial, 1971 (Box 1)